Aitah for lying to my wife that I'd forgive her
cheating. When me and my wife first started
dating, we had a talk about cheating. I straight
up lied and said if this ever happens,
I need to know straight away. If you tell me and
it only happens once, I think I could forgive you.
Fast forward five years later and we are married.
A couple nights ago she came up to me and asked if
I remember our talk. I said which one?
We had a lot of talks like that. The then reminded
me of the cheating talk and confessed she slept
with a co worker at a recent company party. I was
mortified. I packed my stuff and left.
She begged me to stay. I couldn't. I needed to
cool down. We talked yesterday and she again
reminded of our talk early on. I laughed and said
that I never intended to forgive her and I only
said that at the time to make sure she confessed
if it ever happened. I'm still planning on
divorcing her. Nothing can change my mind about
that. But my wife said what I did was
manipulation. Was I the asshole for lying about
forgiving her?